Guide to the World Trade Organization 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
World Trade Organization 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest collection
WTO Seattle collection
1993-2011
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5177
46.85 cubic feet 33 boxes
27 videocassettes and 1 CD Rom disk
5 oversize objects
3 tubes
2 packages
1 vertical file
Protest materials from the 1999 WTO Ministerial Conference held in Seattle
The WTO History Project and its associated archives are largely a response to the momentous protests that took place between November 29 and December 3, 1999 in Seattle during the World Trade Organization Ministerial meetings. The project also documents the mobilization that preceded the Ministerial. The protests were mounted by a wide array of groups and individuals, especially organized labor, environmentalists, and pro-democracy activists concerned that the WTO encouraged trade practices harmful to workers and the environment and operated in a manner which they considered largely undemocratic.
The WTO History Project was a partnership based at the University of Washington that included the Harry Bridges Center for Labor Studies, the Center for Communication and Civic Engagement, and the University Libraries. The groups collaborated to ensure that future researchers of the WTO protests would have access to documentary evidence relating to the range of people involved in the protests, the many strategies and issues they brought to the streets and the meeting rooms, and the coalitions they formed.
During the nearly nine month mobilization in 1999, local and national non-governmental groups representing a variety of interests determined how to publicize the threat posed by the WTO and how to frame their messages to attract the attention of the public, the media and the WTO itself. The lengthy and often contentious mobilization process led to a six-week period immediately preceding the protests during which activists prepared themselves and the public with public teach-ins, training, and debates.
On November 30, 1999, first day of the ministerial meetings, thousands of largely peaceful protestors blocked delegates’ entrance to the opening plenary session. According to press reports, Seattle police in riot gear responded by releasing volleys of tear gas and pepper spray at 10:00 am and continued to do so throughout the day. The police eased up when the 20,000-member labor march reached the downtown core from the Seattle Center, where a large rally had been held. WTO officials cancelled the opening ceremonies. At a time difficult to verify after the fact, Mayor Paul Schell declared a civil emergency, ordering streets to be cleared by 7:00 pm and imposing a curfew on a large area of downtown, from Yesler Way to Denny Way and from Interstate 5 to Elliott Bay. Word of the curfew reached people on the streets at about 4:00 pm. Some dispersed, but others remained and were herded out of downtown by police firing tear gas and pepper spray. At approximately 10:00 pm the State Patrol reinforced the police. Scattered vandalism and looting of several downtown businesses had occurred during the day.
Early the following day, Wednesday, December 1, Seattle police established a ‘demonstration-free zone’ around the WTO meeting site at the Seattle Convention and Trade Center. They severely restricted access to the area, but protests continued. The ministerial meeting was shut down for five hours that day. Governor Gary Locke sent additional State Patrol troopers and two National Guard units to relieve and assist the Seattle police. Clashes between protesters and police spilled over in the evening to Capitol Hill, east of downtown. By then the focus had shifted somewhat, away from the WTO and towards the police response to the protests. Several hundred protesters were arrested, and other protesters demonstrated outside the King County Jail.
The following day the Mayor’s Office reduced the size of what it called a ‘limited curfew zone’ to the area bounded by Fourth Avenue, Pine Street, Boren Avenue, Seneca Street, and Interstate 5. Some protests were staged on Friday, especially inside the convention center. Protestors demonstrated outside the King County jail again on Friday evening. Eventually charges were dropped against most of the over 400 people arrested.
Organized into 15 accessions.
Accession No. 5177-003, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1993-2000
Accession No. 5177-004, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1999
Accession No. 5177-005, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1998-2000 December
Accession No. 5177-006, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1999 October-2000 December
Accession No. 5177-007, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1999-1999
Accession No. 5177-008, World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 2000
Accession No. 5177-009, WTO Seattle collection, 1999
Accession No. 5177-010, WTO Seattle collection, 1999
Accession No. 5177-011, WTO Seattle collection, 1996-2000
Accession No. 5177-012, WTO Seattle collection, 2000
Accession No. 5177-013, WTO Seattle and global justice collection, 1998-2011
Accession No. 5177-014, WTO Seattle collection, 1999-2003
Accession No. 5177-015, Ruth Yarrow WTO Seattle protests collection, 1999
Accession No. 5177-016, World Trade Organization 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference umbrella, bag, and media guide, 1999
Accession No. 5177-017, "No World Trade Without Workers Rights" WTO protest banner, 1999
The WTO Seattle Collection is composed of one large and several smaller accessions. Accession 5177-003, the largest, primarily covers the period from mid-1999 to early 2000. Included are publicity materials, other ephemeral material distributed during various events, reports, published and unpublished writings about the many issues of concern to activists, photos, audio recordings, and communications among the activists who organized events. Oversize items include posters, signs used in teach-ins and protests, and rain ponchos and other objects worn or used in the protests. Personal accounts written after the protests describe the impact the events had on several individuals and often contrast sharply with media accounts of the same events.
Many items in this collection were created by organizations identified in the finding aid as subgroups. Other items were received and kept by these groups to document issues and events. Many gifts of this material were sought and received by WTO History Project staff in the Harry Bridges Center for Labor Studies. Still other batches were collected by interested individuals and forwarded to the Libraries or to the Bridges Center. Subgroups have been established for the following records-creating organizations: the RECORDS SUBGROUP I: DIRECT ACTION NETWORK, a loosely-organized non-hierarchical umbrella organization for groups of protestors; RECORDS SUBGROUP II: EARTHJUSTICE LEGAL DEFENSE FUND, a nonprofit law firm that represents public interest clients; the RECORDS SUBGROUP III: INTERNATIONAL FORUM ON GLOBALIZATION, a coalition of organizations concerned about the effects of globalization; the RECORDS SUBGROUP IV: KING COUNTY LABOR COUNCIL; the Ralph Nader-sponsored RECORDS SUBGROUP V: PEOPLE FOR FAIR TRADE/NETWORK OPPOSED TO WTO and its UW student affiliate organization; and RECORDS SUBGROUP VI: PUBLIC CITIZEN'S GLOBAL TRADE WATCH, a coalition of trade and labor groups. The RECORDS SUBGROUP VII: ALAN RABINOWITZ includes materials contributed by Dr. Rabinowitz, a Seattle resident who helped fund educational activities in advance of the Ministerial. Included in it, besides audio cassettes of World Trade Watch are printed e-mails of preparatory reports, of writings of various friends and contacts of Rabinowitz, of correspondence about the creation of the Independent Media Center, and of news articles.
Although the RECORDS SUBGROUP VIII: NGO COMMITTE FOR THE SEATTLE HOST ORGANIZATION, the organization that sponsored the Ministerial is represented by a subgroup, this segment is very small and consists mainly of packets and other information for delegates.
During processing in 2000-2001, materials were also grouped chronologically within each subgroup. “ Pre-WTO” reflects advance planning and reports about issues posed by the World Trade Organization. “During WTO” documents activities during the week of the Ministerial meetings, November 29-December 3. “Post-WTO” includes subsequent analyses as well as local materials which address the activists’ counter-response to the police actions during the Ministerial week.
Major correspondents include Alan Rabinowitz; Jeremy Simer, an activist with People for Fair Trade/No to WTO; and Patti Goldman, an attorney with the Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund and the environmental community’s representative to the Seattle Host Organization.
Open to all users, but access to portions of the collection is restricted. Contact repository for details.
Goldman, Patti; Rabinowitz, Alan; Simer, Jeremy; AFL-CIO.$bKing County Labor Council of Washington; Direct Action Network; Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund; Institute For Agriculture And Trade Policy; International Forum On Globalization; People For Fair Trade; Public Citizen's Global Trade Watch; World Trade Organization. Ministerial Conference; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Anti-globalization movement$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Protest movements$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Civic Activism; Washington (State); Seattle
- World Trade Organization, 1999 Seattle Ministerial Conference Protest Collection, 1993-2000; 5177-003; 31.17 cubic feet 15 boxes, 3 tubes, 5 oversized objects
  Issue files consisting primarily of clippings as well as organizational files and ephemera used by People for Fair Trade/No To WTO. Records of other organizations such as Direct Action Network, EarthJustice Legal Defense Fund, International Forum On Globalization, King County Labor Council, No To WTO/UW, and Seattle Host Organization NGO Committee include: correspondence, email, calendars, packets, minutes, newsletters, news releases, speeches and writings, publications, ephemera, posters, videotapes, artifacts, maps, lists. Also includes personal accounts, audio tapes, photographs, ephemera, posters, and picket signs, from other sources, documenting opposition groups' preparations for the WTO round in Seattle, WTO week protests and events and the aftermath, 1999-2000.
  View selections from this collection in digital format
  Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers restricted. Contact repository for details.
  - DIRECT ACTION NETWORK (DAN) ), RECORDS SUBGROUP I
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Organizing Packets (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Agenda – Neighborhood Groups Meeting, 8/28/99 (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Subject Series - Street Theater Convergence (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Action Packet (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Bibliographies—News Articles re WTO Protests, 11/30/1999-1/6/2000 (Box-folder 1/7-8)
      - Subject Series
        - Legal Team (Box-folder 1/9)
        - Radical Jeerleaders’ Cheers (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Artifacts (Used at Teach-In, in DAN office, and during Week of WTO) OVERSIZED
        - Flags
          - Yellow/Gray “Resist” (Box-folder 15/1)
          - Red/Blue “Rise Up”
        - Posters
          - “November 30, 1999—Resist the WTO” (Box-folder 15/2)
          - “World Trade Organization—What Are They Trading Away?”
          - “No To WTO!”
          - “Vote”
          - “Alienation”
          - “The WTO is Biocide”
          - “We Oppose the WTO”
          - “Whose World Are They Trading Away?”
          - “Peaceful Protest Zone” (Box-folder 15/3)
          - “Tell the WTO”
          - “Things We Oppose:”
          - “Citizens’ Trade Campaign”
          - “Sierra Club. No Globalization”
        - DAN Legal Team ID Badge (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Part 3: Post-WTO
      - Organization – DAN Continental Confederation (Box-folder 1/12)
      - General Correspondence, 12/99 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Meeting Notes (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Subject Series
        - Legal Team (Box-folder 1/15-17)
        - Medical Collective (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 1/19)
  - EARTHJUSTICE LEGAL DEFENSE FUND, RECORDS SUBGROUP II
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Outgoing Letter, 7/15/99 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Calendars (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Speeches and Writings
        - Goldman, P. and J. Fawcett-Long, Farms and Food Safety At Risk, undated (Box-folder 1/22)
        - Goldman, P. & J. Scott, Our Forests at Risk, 9/1999 (Box-folder 1/23)
        - Goldman, P. & M. Wagner, Trading Away Public Health, 11/1999 (Box-folder 1/24)
        - Puckett, Jim, When Trade is Toxic, 10/1999 (Box-folder 1/25)
        - Wagner, M. & P. Goldman, The Case for Rethinking the WTO, 11/1999 (Box-folder 1/26)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Subject Series
        - Billboard Campaign (Box-folder 1/28)
        - Coffee, Birds and Trade Policy, 10/1999 (Box-folder 1/29)
        - Environmental Media Services Briefing (Box-folder 1/30)
        - Sierra Club - Bioinvasions (Box-folder 1/31)
        - Trade Pacts, 7/24/99 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - Newsletters – WTO News: The Road To Seattle, 9/10 – 10/20/99 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - News Release, 12/1/99 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Ephemera, 9/7/99 (Box-folder 1/35)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Calendars & Schedules (Box-folder 1/37)
      - Lists – Delegates and Observers (Box-folder 1/38)
      - Videotape—The WTO’s Race to the Bottom (Box-folder 1/39)
      - Newsletter – World Trade Observer, Nov-Dec. 1999 (Box-folder 1/40-41)
      - News Release, 12/1/99 (Box-folder 1/42)
      - Photographs (Negatives only) (Box-folder 1/43)
  - INTERNATIONAL FORUM ON GLOBALIZATION, RECORDS SUBGROUP III:
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Organization (Box-folder 1/44)
      - News Release (Box-folder 1/45)
      - Timeline—The Trouble With Trade, 1944-1999 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - Report – “Beyond The WTO”, 12/26/99 (Box-folder 1/47)
      - List – WTO Publications (Box-folder 1/48)
      - Speeches and Writings
        - Anderson, Sarah, Ed., Views From the South, undated (Box-folder 1/49)
        - Barker, D. & J. Mander, Invisible Government, 10/99 (Box-folder 1/50)
        - Clarke, Tony, By What Authority!, undated (Box-folder 1/51)
        - Menotti, Victor, Free Trade, Free Logging, 11/99 (Box-folder 1/52)
        - Unidentified, “Eight Myths of Economic Globalization”, undated (Box-folder 1/53)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Audiocassettes (2)—Teach-In, 11/26-27/99 (Box-folder 1/54)
      - Videotape—Town Hall Debate, 11/30/99 (Box-folder 1/55)
      - Invitation (Box-folder 1/56)
      - News Releases (Box-folder 1/57)
  - KING COUNTY LABOR COUNCIL, RECORDS SUBGROUP IV
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Incoming Letter – Labor Party. Seattle Chapter, undated (Box-folder 1/58)
      - Outgoing Letter - Invitation to Student Activists re WTO Rally, 11/3/1999 (Box-folder 1/59)
      - Planning Packet (Box-folder 1/60)
      - Packet – “Workers’ Rights and the World Trade Organization (AFL-CIO) (Box-folder 1/61)
      - Subject Series
        - Baskin, Martha, 8/2/99-2/12/2000 (Box-folder 1/62)
        - Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box-folder 1/63)
        - Herman, Alexis, US Secretary of Labor, Speech, 10/25/1999 (Box-folder 1/64)
        - Port Truck Driver Campaign, 9/99 (Box-folder 1/65)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 9/99 (Box-folder 1/66)
      - Newsletters—Labor’s Voice, 10/99 (Box-folder 1/67)
      - Speeches and Writings (Box-folder 1/68)
        - Feldman, Rich, “New Rules For the Global Economy”, 9/15/99
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 1/69)
    - Part 2: Post-WTO
      - Speeches and Writings – Ohio AFL-CIO President, 2/15/00 (Box-folder 1/70)
  - NO! TO WTO--UW, RECORDS SUBGROUP V:
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Incoming Letters – King County Labor Council, 11/3/99 (Box-folder 1/71)
      - Newsletters
        - Corporate Watch, 9/98-8/99 (Box-folder 1/72)
        - Eat The State, 9&11/99 (Box-folder 1/73)
        - Justice, 9-10/99
        - Ruckus
        - Sweatshop Watch, 10/20/99 (Box-folder 1/74)
      - Personal Account – Ramy Khalil (Box-folder 1/75)
      - Subject Series
        - Committees (Box-folder 1/76)
        - Maquiladora Industry, 10/20/99 (Box-folder 1/77)
      - Guides For Organizers (Box-folder 1/78-80)
      - Background Facts re WTO (Box-folder 1/81)
      - Surveys (Box-folder 1/82)
      - Speeches and Writings
        - Hyde, David, “The WTO Does Not Affect You!”, 11/28/99 (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Murphy, Gillian & L. Mogford and D. Hyde, “A Marxist Analysis of the World Trade Organization”, 10/25/99 (Box-folder 2/2)
        - Unidentified, “Welcome fellow Students!”, 11/30/99 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Speeches and Writings by Others
        - Clinton, Bill. Remarks By the President at the Democratic Leadership Council Gala, 10/13/99 (Box-folder 2/4)
        - Lucas, Caroline, Watchful In Seattle, 11/99 (Box-folder 2/5)
        - Miller, Scott. Director, National Government Relations, Proctor & Gamble. Statement Before the Interagency Trade Policy Staff Committee, 6/7/99 (Box-folder 2/6)
        - Schweke, William and Robert K. Stumberg, Could Economic Development Become Illegal In the New Global Policy Environment?, 7/99 (Box-folder 2/7)
        - Copies of Published Articles (Box-folder 2/8-16)
      - Clippings (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Organizer’s Guide (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Ephemera
        - Student Walkout (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Misc. (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Part 3: Post-WTO
      - Newsletter – Ruckus, 1/2000 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 2/23)
  - PEOPLE FOR FAIR TRADE/NO TO WTO, RECORDS SUBGROUP VI
    - Part 1: Pre-WTO
      - Organization - Website (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Incoming Letters, 8/6 – 9/7/99 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Outgoing Letters, 7/30/99 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Meeting Notes, 7/9 – 8/24/00 (Box-folder 2/27-28)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Calendars (Box-folder 2/30-31)
      - Pledge Cards (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Lists
        - Ballard Meeting Facilities (Box-folder 2/33)
        - Experts, Speakers, Meeting Attendance (Box-folder 2/34)
        - Media Web Sites (Box-folder 2/35-36)
        - Websites (Box-folder 2/37)
        - WTO Project (Box-folder 2/38)
      - Maps (Box-folder 2/39)
      - Telephone Logs 11/18/99 – 3/14/00 CLOSED until 5/2005 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Packet–“Loaded against the poor, World Trade Organisation” Oxfam (Box-folder 2/40)
      - Newsletters
        - Buckhorn Bulletin, 8/99 (Box-folder 2/41)
        - Center Focus, 11/99
        - Corporate Europe Observer, 7/99
        - Drillbits & Tailings, 10/23/99 (Box-folder 2/42)
        - High Country News, 9/97 (Box-folder 2/43)
        - Report From Washington, 2/6/98 (Box-folder 2/44)
        - Washington Trout Report1998 (Box-folder 2/45)
      - Publications
        - Asia Pacific Environmental Exchange, 11/99, n.d (Box-folder 2/46)
        - “Handbood for Nonviolent Action” (Box-folder 2/47)
        - Multinational Monitor, 10-11/99 (Box-folder 2/48)
        - NAFTA Superhighways, 1998 (Box-folder 2/49)
        - “One Big Movement, Creating the End of Corporate Rule”, undated (Box-folder 2/50)
        - “The WTO, Global Capitalism and the Socialist Alternative” publ. by Justice (Box-folder 2/51)
      - Writing – Madsen, Jeremy, 9/4/99 (Box-folder 2/52)
      - Speeches and Writings by Others
        - Statements re: International Day of Action Against the WTO, 9/15/99 (Box-folder 2/53)
        - Collingsworth, Terry, “U.S. Advocacy for Reform of the WTO—Progress or Posturing?”, undated (Box-folder 2/54)
        - Cornwell, Rachel and Andrew Wells, “Deploying Insecurity”, 1999 (Box-folder 2/55)
        - Korten, David C., The Lexus and the Olive Tree A Book Review, undated (Box-folder 2/56)
        - Lamy, Pascal, “Communication from the Trade DG of the European Commission”, 10/6/99 (Box-folder 2/57)
        - Mokhiber, Russell & Robert Weissman, “10 Reasons to Dismantle the WTO”, undated (Box-folder 2/58)
        - Unidentified, “Ministerial Decision on Trade, Globalisation, Development and Labour Issues”, 3/12/99 (Box-folder 2/59)
        - Newsletter Articles from e-Newsletters (Box-folder 2/60)
      - Fact Sheets (Box-folder 2/61)
      - Subject Series
        - Adbusters Originals, undated (Box-folder 2/62)
        - Animal Rights, 1999 (Box-folder 2/63)
        - Ballard-Fremont Neighborhood, 8/99 (Box-folder 2/64)
        - Bananas, 1999 (Box-folder 2/65)
        - Churches, 1999 (Box-folder 2/66-67)
        - Clise Property, 1999 (Box-folder 2/68)
        - Delegate Visa Problems, 11/8/1999 (Box-folder 2/69)
        - Democracy/Legalities, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 2/70-74)
        - Downtown Seattle Association, 1999 (Box-folder 2/75)
        - Education/Youth, 1999 (Box-folder 2/76)
        - Environment Issues, 10 – 11/99 (Box-folder 2/77)
        - Forests, undated (Box-folder 2/78)
        - Fundraisers, 10/4/99 (Box-folder 2/79)
        - Health, 6/99, n.d. (Box-folder 2/80-81)
        - Joint Pledge Card Proposal, 1999 (Box-folder 2/82)
        - King County Council Resolution, 8-9/99 (Box-folder 2/83)
        - Labor, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 2/84-86)
        - Larson, Eric, undated (Box-folder 2/87)
        - Logistics, 11/99, nd. (Box-folder 2/88-89)
        - Methodist Church, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 2/90)
        - NGO Press Center, 11/99 (Box-folder 2/91)
        - Neighborhood Organizations, 8-9/99 (Box-folder 2/92)
        - No! WTO Student Teach-In, 11/6/99 (Box-folder 2/93)
        - “The Opposition”—CIBER/UW, Simer, Jeremy, 7/99, n.d. (Box-folder 2/94)
        - “The Opposition”—WTO & SHO Information, Simer, Jeremy, 1999 (Box-folder 2/95)
        - Seattle Student/Youth Organizing, 8-9/99 (Box-folder 2/96)
        - Social Justice, 1999 (Box-folder 2/97-101)
        - Street Committee, 8/25/99 (Box-folder 2/102)
        - Trade/WTO Anti-Corp, 1998-99 (Box-folder 2/103-105)
        - Trade/WTO Pro-Trade, n.d. (Box-folder 2/106)
        - Trade/WTO—Trade Treaties, 1993-99 (Box-folder 2/107-110)
        - Volunteers, 9-11/99 (Box-folder 2/111)
        - Washington Council on International Trade, 5/2000 (Box-folder 2/112)
        - Workers & Families For Free Trade, n.d. (Box-folder 2/113)
      - Notice re Noise Ordinance (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Resolutions - Labor (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Conference - Evergreen State College, 10/23-24/1999 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Graphics (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Notes (Box-folder 3/5)
      - News Releases (Box-folder 3/6-7)
      - Ephemera (Box-folder 3/8-11)
      - Chronological Files (Mostly clippings), 6/99-11/28/99 (Box-folder 3/12-27)
      - Clippings, 11/24-25/1999 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Clippings - Articles, In-Depth (Box-folder 3/29-38)
      - Posters OVERSIZED
        - Information about WTO and its record --Foamboard 3-panel (Box-folder 14/1)
        - No To WTO Teach-In, 11/6/99 (Box-folder Tube 17)
    - Part 2: During WTO
      - Schedule (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Notebook – “Front Desk Information” (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Speeches and Writings
        - Chants (Box-folder 3/38)
        - Humane Society of the United States, 11/29/99 (Box-folder 3/39)